William Wentworth

CONTACT

Indianapolis, IN

E-mail: WWentworth@Live.com

Phone: (317) 457-6006

SUMMARY

Resourceful and quick-thinking Team Leader with 15 years warehouse and supply chain environment. bringing a combination of strong leadership skills and the ability to motivate team members. Highly adaptable and competent in learning new tasks. Track record of achieving exceptional results and maintaining exceptional quality.

WORK EXPERIENCE

The Home Depot

March 2018 - Present

Lead Master Technician

- Organize, train, and oversee a team of technicians in a high speed warehouse environment.
- Provide performance input on technicians to the Management Team
- Work with operations via E-mail and ticketing system to properly meet all demands and expectations.
- Troubleshoot and repair of small engines, outdoor power equipment, and electrical devices.
- Manage and maintain tool inventory.
- Work with the office team to ensure all repairs and services are completed and on schedule.
- Maintain accurate records of preventative maintenance, inventory, service requests and status of all repairs.

Support.com

June 2015 - March 2018

Remote Services Technician

- Answer inbound calls and greet customers.
- Resolve customer requests by investigating problems, developing solutions and recommend additional products and/or services relevant to assessment of the customer needs.
- Properly document all customer interactions.
- Use company provided tools and process to troubleshoot and solve customer technology problems.
- Communicate with others, verbally and in writing, technical information, job procedure recommendations, and other work-related information.

Fedex Express

August 2005 - June 2015

Team Lead

- Work with Manager in the assignment and supervision of personnel in order to achieve an efficient operation at all times.
- Assist the Management Team with daily workflow

William Wentworth

- Assist couriers in analyzing and correcting problems encountered during operations.
- Allocating jobs and workloads to staff members based on their ability and experience across 30 warehouse locations
- Provide accuracy information to the Management Team on key Issues.
- Assist when needed in processing of freight to complete tasks on time.

Walmart

March 2009 - June 2012

Technician

- Removing, installing, repairing, and balancing tires for optimal vehicular function.
- Changing vehicle fluids, filters, and providing lubrication for automobile maintenance.
- Provide efficient customer service based upon the individual needs of the customer's vehicle.
- Document technical and system work performed for each vehicle.
- Participated in factory-sponsored training classes to remain up-to-date with industry trends.

QUALIFICATIONS

- Working knowledge of Warehouse and Supply Chain environment.
- Excellent written and verbal communication skills as well as excellent interpersonal skills.
- Proven planning and organizing skills, leadership, teamwork, and influencing or collaboration skills.
- Strong IT and Computer skills for an ever-growing reliance on technology in the field with a Comptia IT Certification.
- Excellent project and time management, analytical and problem solving skills.
- Proficient with Office including Excel, Word, and Outlook.

EDUCATION

High School Diploma

2001 - 2005

Northwest High School

CERTIFICATIONS

Comptia A+ Certification

William Wentworth 2